# Wachirawut Phungirnngok

135 Moo 6, Bann Seaw, Hua-Ngua district, Yang Talad, Kalasin. 46120 0833609498 (Mobile) longgong1987@gmail.com

RESUME SUMMARY		
Latest Position	Web Developer	
Years(s) of Work Experience	4 years	
Latest Job Function	Information Technology (IT)	
Latest Industry Sector	Information Technology	
Latest Career Level	Entry Level	
Highest Education Attained	Degree	
Authorized to work in Thailand	Yes	
Availability	After - 01/03/2016	



### PERSONAL PARTICULARS

Male
29
18-Mar-87
Thailand
Single
Northeastern > Others
46120

#### EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

My name is Wachirawut Phungirnngok, I'm interest and love web developments, design, ux/ui design and coding. But I choose coding in main career path and now interest in MEAN

Over 4 years web development work experience, I developed myself better in many ways.

For example:

- Work with develop team and learning about division of duties and responsibilities.
- Learning AngularJS, ExpressJS, NodeJS from Udemy course
- Learning a new web, database technology and UX/UI to design systems and user interface to user friendly
- Meeting with customers to analyse the problems and requirement of the customer.
- Consulting and troubleshooting customer's problem.

My strengths is always develop myself to learning new technology, responsible in the work assignment and has the ability to endure pressure.

# **EDUCATION**

#### 2006 - 2010

Khon Kaen University, Bachelor of arts(Information Science) (major: Information Science)

Grade / GPA: 3.10

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Dreambase Interactive** Web Develope

Dec / 2014 - Present THB 28,000

- Building and coding backend contents management for Dtac Watchever app(iOS, Androind)

URL: http://www.pomohouse.com/

- CSS, HTML Responsive for Pomohouse website (e-commerce)
- Building and coding backend of Pomohouse website (e-commerce)

URL: http://ourmaterdei.com/demo/

- Frontend for Ourmeterdei website(responsive)

Forviz Co., Ltd. Web Developer

Feb / 2011 - Nov / 2014 THB 20,000

- Website : http://www.forviz.com • Backend, Frontend Programming.
- Analyse and design system, database from customer requirement.
- Development website support mobile, tablet devices, modern browser and ie8+
- Agile by using scrum and work as team.
- . Consulting and solutions to the customer

For example task project :

- 1. You are the FACE of Toyota(2012-2014): http://www.youarethefaceoftoyota.com
- As evaluate system for employee and dealer nationwide.
- Calculate score and show on employee, dealer report page.
- Can report score, ranking, strength, weakness by pdf file.
  Backend : report evaluate on web and excel report.
- 2. Greyhound Online Shop: https://www.greyhound.co.th/onlineshop/
- Backend programming: manage products, booking orders, set news letter send to subscriber
- Frontend programming: show products by group and catgory, add product to cart, check out and payment gateway for order. member system, wishlist and newsletter subscribe
- 3. The Key (Land & houses): http://thekey.lh.co.th
- Responsive support
- Backend can add, edit, update, delete new condo project.
- Frontend can select project to see project information, gallery, progress and contact sales
- 4. Amarin Plaza: http://www.amarinplaza.com
- Backend can add, edit, update, delete news, promotion and other contents.
- search shops directory
- Dining and Shopping to group shops by categories or floors

- CMS for manage units of Magnolias Waterfront Residences ICONSIAM.
- Manage bookings and payments.
  API for iPad app to get project information, units informations, price, booking status by using JSON

- Export, print or send email for quotation, booking form and invoice.
   Sales report by daily and by individual.

# 6. CMS Directory

- CMS for shopping mall.
  Manage shops and kios information.
  Manage news, promotion by shop owner. They can add, edit or delete by themself.
  Admin can send message to notify shops for news or some information and shop can send message to admin for contact information.
  Export XML for touchscreen shopping mall.

\* Forviz Co., Ltd. moved from Perfect vision Multimedia Co., Ltd.

# SKILLS (OPTIONAL)

- PHP framework : Laravel, Yii, Codeigniter
- MySQL, MongoDB(interest and learning)
- jQuery, JSON, XML, SASS, CSS2/CSS3, HTML
- Interest and Learning NodeJS, ExpressJS, AngularJS
- Wordpress : modified and custom theme, Woocommerce
- Responsive web development
- Jira, Bitbucket, Source Tree, Git repository

# LANGUAGES (OPTIONAL)

Spoken: Thai (strong), English(fair) Written: Thai (strong), English(fair)

# PERSONAL WEBSITES (OPTIONAL)

LinkedIn: http://th.linkedin.com/in/longgong1987/

